{
    "id": "5a1f7ddd17764bafa0e30ff2e80b95ef",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. to the manager about my holiday in the morning.",
            "description": "The simple past is used to say that something happened at some point in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "had spoken",
                "have spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………. to the theatre last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. the pictures on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hanged",
                "hunged"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship has ……………………………….",
            "description": "People drown ships and boats sink.",
            "answers": [
                "sank",
                "sunk",
                "drowned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I went there I found that he ……………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………… to me since our last meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't speak",
                "hasn't spoken",
                "hadn't spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………………. tennis every day.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "are playing",
                "have played"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of the messengers ……………………………… returned.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after either and neither. ",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of these apples ……………………………… not good.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun quality hence, a singular verb should be used.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Death ……………………………… his icy hand on all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lies",
                "lay",
                "lays"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………… it a moment ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hears",
                "heard",
                "have heard"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………… there for the last two hours.",
            "description": "To talk about an action or situation that started in the past and has continued up to the present, use the present perfect or present perfect continuous. ",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "has been waiting",
                "was waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}